markspace.com 2018-12-14

# Privacy Policy - Mark/Space

Policy in effect as of: 26 March 2013

Any personally identifiable information (including without limitation your name and email address, and any data or meta data you have elected to store with fliq.markspace.com (our “Service”) via web browser, mobile device, or other approved electronic devices or personal computer) collected or provided to Mark/Space hereunder shall be collected, secured and maintained in accordance with any applicable privacy laws governing the collection, use or storage of such personally identifiable information (“Privacy Restricted Data”). The collection, access, use, maintenance and disclosure of Privacy Restricted Data shall comply with all applicable international, federal, state and local laws, rules and regulations as they may be amended from time to time (the “Privacy Laws”).

In accordance with applicable law and/or Mark/Space policies and procedures, all Privacy Restricted Data collected shall originate from users who have provided explicit (“opt-in”) consent to the collection, access, use, maintenance and disclosure of the Privacy Restricted Data. For the avoidance of doubt, creating an account and accessing this Service shall constitute consent.

Mark/Space shall collect, use, access, maintain, and disclose or share Privacy Restricted Data only for the benefit of Mark/Space and only to the extent strictly necessary to perform its obligations under this Agreement, or as otherwise required by law.

Mark/Space shall not use or modify the Privacy Restricted Data, commercially exploit it, disclose it or do any other thing that may in any manner adversely affect the integrity, security or confidentiality of such Privacy Restricted Data, other than as expressly specified herein or as directed by Mark/Space in writing.

In no event shall Mark/Space disclose any Privacy Restricted Data to any third party except to the extent strictly necessary to provide the Service and perform its obligations under this Agreement, and in such case, only as permitted by law and subject to a binding agreement requiring the same level of data privacy, protection and information security as required hereunder. Notwithstanding anything above, Mark/Space may disclose Privacy Restricted Data if required by applicable law, if Mark/Space has a good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to comply with legal process or public policy, or to protect the public, an individual’s personal safety, or the property or interests of Mark/Space. Under such circumstances, Mark/Space may be prohibited from providing notice of the disclosure, and Mark/Space reserve the right not to provide such notice in our sole discretion.

In the event Mark/Space participates in a merger, acquisition, or form of sale of some or all of its assets, we may transfer Privacy Restricted Data as part of that transaction, in order that the Services provided to you can be continued by that party.

### Updates to this policy

We reserve the right to make make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make changes, we will update the effective date at the top of this policy. You should periodically review this agreement to keep up to date with our procedures and policies. Your continued use of the Services constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.
